{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Storm \u0026 Security Shutter Repair Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40411/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40411,"taskName":"Security or Storm Shutters - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair or Service Security or Storm Shutters","xmTaskDescriptor":"Storm \u0026 Security Shutter Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":218,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Security Storm system alarms protection","textMessagingName":"Repr Storm Shut","rolloverLongDesc":"These come in many forms, but are nearly always made of metal \u0026 can either be removed, rolled up, pivoted, slid or folded out of the way when not in use. The three most common types are storefront shutters used in urban areas, hurricane shutters in storm-prone areas \u0026 entranceway gates for mansions. This includes repairs \u0026 adjustments to the gates \u0026 shutters, their retraction mechanisms, remote control devices \u0026 locking mechanisms.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes riot, hurricane \u0026 entrance gates or shutters.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Service Security or Storm Shutters.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Storm \u0026 Security Shutter Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix or Restore Storm Shutters","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":67,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Security or Storm Shutters Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Security or Storm Shutters - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Security or Storm Shutter Project","urlName":"Security-or-Storm-Shutters-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Storm Shutter Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor | Security Shutters Repair","searchKeywords":"Security,Storm,system,alarms,protection,windows,surveillance,sercuirty,secure,safe,protect,exterior,burglar,Shutters","emcCategoryOid":-12043,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":704,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564373324358pwspr009F22724D8FA4DFF8FD65C05DD318E5A42.pwspr009-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40411/":{"taskOID":40411,"originalTaskOID":40411,"setID":704,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4983,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Repair","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of the repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4532,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"PVC slats are cracked, broken","answerDisplayText":"PVC slats are cracked, broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5664,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Shutter is loose","answerDisplayText":"Shutter is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5662,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Shutter is bent/dented","answerDisplayText":"Shutter is bent/dented","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4211,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"No longer locks into place","answerDisplayText":"No longer locks into place","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4212,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"No longer retractable","answerDisplayText":"No longer retractable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1978,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Doesn't move properly on track","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't move properly on track","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3971,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Motor doesn't work properly","answerDisplayText":"Motor doesn't work properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1710,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Crank doesn't work properly","answerDisplayText":"Crank doesn't work properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6801,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Want to add motor","answerDisplayText":"Want to add motor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6802,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Want to add remote control","answerDisplayText":"Want to add remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6804,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Want to add switch indoors","answerDisplayText":"Want to add switch indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6805,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Want to add timer","answerDisplayText":"Want to add timer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6797,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Want to add electronic sensor","answerDisplayText":"Want to add electronic sensor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4983,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Repair","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of the repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4532,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"PVC slats are cracked, broken","answerDisplayText":"PVC slats are cracked, broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5664,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Shutter is loose","answerDisplayText":"Shutter is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5662,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Shutter is bent/dented","answerDisplayText":"Shutter is bent/dented","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4211,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"No longer locks into place","answerDisplayText":"No longer locks into place","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4212,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"No longer retractable","answerDisplayText":"No longer retractable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1978,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Doesn't move properly on track","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't move properly on track","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3971,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Motor doesn't work properly","answerDisplayText":"Motor doesn't work properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1710,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Crank doesn't work properly","answerDisplayText":"Crank doesn't work properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6801,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Want to add motor","answerDisplayText":"Want to add motor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6802,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Want to add remote control","answerDisplayText":"Want to add remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6804,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Want to add switch indoors","answerDisplayText":"Want to add switch indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6805,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Want to add timer","answerDisplayText":"Want to add timer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6797,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Want to add electronic sensor","answerDisplayText":"Want to add electronic sensor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4532,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"PVC slats are cracked, broken","answerDisplayText":"PVC slats are cracked, broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5664,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Shutter is loose","answerDisplayText":"Shutter is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5662,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Shutter is bent/dented","answerDisplayText":"Shutter is bent/dented","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4211,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"No longer locks into place","answerDisplayText":"No longer locks into place","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4212,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"No longer retractable","answerDisplayText":"No longer retractable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1978,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Doesn't move properly on track","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't move properly on track","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3971,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Motor doesn't work properly","answerDisplayText":"Motor doesn't work properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1710,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Crank doesn't work properly","answerDisplayText":"Crank doesn't work properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6801,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Want to add motor","answerDisplayText":"Want to add motor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6802,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Want to add remote control","answerDisplayText":"Want to add remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6804,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Want to add switch indoors","answerDisplayText":"Want to add switch indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6805,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Want to add timer","answerDisplayText":"Want to add timer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6797,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Want to add electronic sensor","answerDisplayText":"Want to add electronic sensor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}